[

Get Payouts for ZEC, ETC, RVN, ERG, KAS, NEXA mining in BTC](https://2miners.com/blog/get-paid-in-bitcoin-for-altcoin-mining-btc-payouts-for-gpu-mined-etc-ergo-rvn/ "Get Payouts for ZEC, ETC, RVN, ERG, KAS, NEXA mining in BTC")

–

Mining Profit Calculator
------------------------

ENRUTRESPTDEZH

AUDBGNCADCHFCNYEURGBPHUFIDRINRJPYKRWMXNPLNRSDRUBTHBTRYUAHUSDVND

We welcome you to participate in 2CryptoCalc.com project. If you found some mistake in GPU hashrates or if you just want to refine some - please make a request on [GitHub](https://github.com/2miners/2cryptocalc-hashrates) or write us in [Telegram Chat](https://t.me/chat2miners). We would be pleased to apply it.

© 2019-2024, [2Cryptocalc.com](https://2cryptocalc.com/)

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Statement relating to the services provided on the website http://2cryptocalc.com ("Website")
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

By Using the Website, or otherwise providing personal information to Us, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy and you consent to Our using the personal information provided in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Our related Terms and Conditions set out the terms upon which we are willing to provide our services to you through the Website and otherwise.

The following terminology applies to this Privacy Statement and any or all Agreements:

"Miner", “You” and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the 2CryptoCalc mining profit calculator terms and conditions. "The Calculator", "Calculator", “Ourselves”, “We” and "Us", refers to the mining profit calculator service. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.

WE INTEND TO USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION PRIMARILY TO PROVIDE OUR SERVICES ONLY AND TO COMMUNICATE AND MARKET THESE AND FUTURE SERVICES AND PRODUCTS AND SERVICES OF OTHER BUSINESS PARTNERS THAT WE FEEL MAY BE OF INTEREST OF YOU. WE WILL NEVER SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO UNRELATED THIRD PARTIES.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user actions, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within this Calculator on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit permission.

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES.

English

USD

We welcome you to participate in 2CryptoCalc.com project. If you found some mistake in GPU hashrates or if you just want to refine some - please make a request on [GitHub](https://github.com/2miners/2cryptocalc-hashrates) or write us in [Telegram Chat](https://t.me/chat2miners). We would be pleased to apply it.

© 2019—2024, [2Cryptocalc.com](#top)
